Front-End Developer

PROFILE

I have always been attracted to art & technology, but an important milestone for me was when I came to Barcelona for a master's degree in Digital Arts. There, I discovered programming could be a thing of beauty, too. Since then, I have focused on turning wireframe sketches into interactive websites. Many years have gone by and I still love working on a project that makes me learn new tools. I believe it is a virtuous loop of high quality work and self improvement.

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS & Javascript
- Libraries & Frameworks
- Responsive Design
- Testing / Debugging
- Version Control / GIT
- Command Line (GUI)

WORK_EXPERIENCE

CREATIVE HOTHOUSE

_Front-End_Developer

January 2014 → Present

I focused on the development, deployment and maintenance of several responsive and usable web projects, which ranged from static landing pages and email marketing campaigns to e-commerce sites, complex multi user dashboards and dynamic web apps.

As a result, I am well versed using HTML, CSS, SASS, Foundation, Bootstrap, Element, Semantic, Javascript, JQuery, AngularJS, Vue, Vuex, Git, Magento, NPM, Gulp, Webpack and anything I could find and learn to complete a specific task more easily and efficiently.

GREY SPAIN

_Interactive_Developer

May 2013 → December 2013 && May 2008 → January 2010

I was in charge of developing banners, minisites, forms, galleries and newsletters for SEAT Spain. I worked for this multinational advertisement agency on two different occasions, but my position was very much the same. I used mainly Flash (Actionscript 3) and HTML, using the DoubleClick technology.

Λ∠

STUDIO+44

_Interactive_Developer

February 2012 → November 2012

My job consisted of making banners, videos and email templates for our international clients (mainly UK). Nike, HSBC, Ballantines were some of them.

EVIL LOVE

_Flash_Developer

May 2011 → October 2011

My main tasks were the production of banners, videos and email campaigns for the agency's customer portfolio, which included LaCaixa, Tourline Express, Zurich, Gas Natural, among others.

EDUCATION

M.A. DIGITAL ARTS

_Universidad_Pompeu_Fabra 2004 → 2005

B.A. COMMUNICATION STUDIES

_Universidad_De_Lima (Perú)

1995 → 1999